杰森 · 兰斯托夫: 做的很少，我已经设置了一个主题。
&gt;&gt; Jason Lengstorf: Having done
very little, I’ve set up a theme.
现在，如果我重新启动网站，什么都不会发生
Now, nothing’s really gonna
happen if I restart the site
因为没有任何组件访问任何
with this theme installed, because none
of the components are accessing any of
默认的主题-ui 的东西。
the default theme-ui stuff.
所以在我们真正看到它工作之前，我们要添加一个布局文件。
So before we can really see it work,
we’re gonna add a layout file.
所以让我们创建组件 / layout. js，在这里面,
So let's create components/layout.js,
and inside of this,
我们要抓住 JSX pragma 从主题-ui，所以我们可以使用 SX 道具。
we're gonna grab that JSX pragma from
theme-ui so that we can use the SX prop.
然后我还想得到,
And then I also want to get,
我们要用 global 因为
we're gonna use global because
我们想覆盖几个,
we wanna override a couple,
基本上就是利润之类的东西。
basically just the margins and stuff.
我们要用“情感 / 核心”来覆盖它。
And we're gonna override
that from @emotion/core.
我们将从盖茨比导入链接，因为我们将连接到。
We'll import link from gatsby because
we're gonna be linking to things.
因为我不想在输出中添加任何垃圾,
And then because I don't wanna
add any junk in my output,
我还要导入碎片从反应，因为我想能够使用它。
I'm also gonna import fragment from react,
because I want to be able to use that.
那么让我们来定义一下我们的布局。
So let's define our layout.
在我忘记之前，让我们确保将其作为默认值导出。
And before I forget, let's make sure
that we export that as our default.
好吧。
Okay.
所以布局会让孩子们做道具。
So the layout's gonna
get children as a prop.
这只是在组件内部传递的任何信息。
That's just anything that gets
passed inside that component.
我们甚至不需要花括号。
And we don't even need curly braces.
我们只需要直接返回。
We're just gonna do a direct return.
我们来做一个片段。
We'll do a fragment.
在这个片段中，我们将从 global 开始。
And inside that fragment
we'll start out with global.
我们要设定风格。
And we wanna set styles.
还有一件事情会发生在情感核心上
And so another thing that will
happen with the emotion core
它也会接受主题对象作为函数的参数。
global is that it also will accept the
theme object as an argument to a function.
虽然这不是主题界面的一部分,
So even though this isn't
technically part of theme-ui,
我们仍然可以访问这个主题对象并使用它。
we can still get access to
that theme object and use it.
我们就这样做，然后回来，我会做一些事情。
So let's do that and we will return,
I'm gonna do a couple things.
我不认为我会在主题上这么做,
I don't think I would do this in a theme,
但是因为这是一个网站，我很高兴在这里做一些广泛的宣传。
but since it's a site, I am happy to
make some sweeping proclamations here.
所以我要说 boxsize 等于 border-box。
So I'm gonna say boxSizing
is gonna equal border-box.
这将给我们一些更多的可预测性周围的东西呈现方式。
That will give us some more predictability
around the way that things render.
我还要在主体上说，我希望字体家族相等
I'm also going to say on the body
that I want the font family to equal
Theme.fonts.body 所以我们要使用 body 字体作为默认字体。
theme.fonts.body, so we're gonna
use the body font as the default.
我会设置字体大小为20，使它更大一点，更容易阅读。
I will set the font size to 20,
make it a little bigger, easier to read.
然后我把边距设置为0。
Then I'm going to set the margin to 0.
在这下面，我们需要一个标题。
Underneath this, we need a header.
所以对于我的头部，我将使用我的标准模式，即使用
So for my header, I'm going to use
my standard pattern, which is to use
原色作为背景色，背景色作为文本色,
the primary color as the background and
the background color as the text color,
然后我们给它加点填充物，这样它就不会被压扁了。
and then we'll give it a little bit
of padding so it's not all squished.
在它里面，我们会做一个主页的链接
And inside of it,
we will do a link to the homepage and
给它加点风格。
give that a little bit of style.
所以我们说颜色就是背景,
So we'll say that the color is
going to be the background,
因为它是一个链接，默认情况下它不会继承标题颜色。
because it's a link it won't inherit
the header color by default.
我们还要将 fontweight 设置为 bold。
We're also going to set
the fontweight to bold.
我们希望文字装饰是无，因为它将是一种标志为
We want the text decoration to be none
because it's gonna be kind of a logo for
这个地点。
the site.
然后我想集中注意力，因为我们想确保
And then I want to set on focus,
because we wanna make sure that it's
键盘可以操作，但我们还是希望它看起来漂亮，就像它是我们主题的一部分。
keyboard navigable, but we still want it
to look nice, like it's part of our theme.
所以我要设置轮廓，我要把这个主题对象。
So I'm gonna set the outline and
I'm gonna pull in this theme object.
我想要的轮廓是2px 的固体，我想使用的主题颜色。
And I want the outline to be 2px solid,
and I wanna use the theme color.
因此，让我们使用背景颜色的主题。
So let's use the background color for
the theme.
然后因为我不想它被链接压扁,
And then because I don't want it
to be squished up on the link,
我要做 outlineOffset。
I'm gonna do the outlineOffset.
我们会把它变成4个。
And we'll make that 4.
好的，然后我可以设置标题。
Okay, so then I can set the title.
我们称之为内格罗尼鉴赏协会。
We'll call this
the Negroni Appreciation Society.
如果我能把社会这个词拼对。
If I can spell society right.
好，很好，很好。
Okay, good good.
然后我们需要一个主要部分，所以我们只是希望这不要被挤压，所以
Then we need a main section, so
we just want this to not be squished, so
我们设置一个竖轴，y 轴是上下的。
we'll set a vertical, so
the y-axis is up and down.
我们把差距设定为4。
We'll set that margin to 4.
我们将左右边距设置为自动，使其居中。
We'll set the left right margin to auto so
that it centers.
我要设置一个最大宽度为650像素，我们将设置一个宽度
I'm gonna set a max width of 650 pixels,
and we'll set a width
90个垂直宽度的单位，这样它就不会在较小的屏幕上粉碎。
of 90 vertical width units so
that it doesn't smash on smaller screens.
在里面我们经过孩子们。
And inside we pass the children.
好的，这是一个布局部分。
Okay, that's a layout component.
现在让我们使用这个布局组件。
So now let's go use this layout component.
我们可以直接跳到我们的页面并导入它。
And we can do that by just jumping
into our pages and importing it.
这就是我们想要的结果。
And that'll be what we want to happen.
那么，让我们进入我们的页面。
So let's go into our pages.
我要从组件 / 布局导入布局。
I'm gonna import layout
from components/layout.
然后在这里，我可以使用它。
And then here, I can just use that.
杰森 · 兰斯托夫: 好的，这是一个。
&gt;&gt; Jason Lengstorf: Okay, so that's one.
对这个也做同样的事情。
Do the same thing on this one.
从组件 / 布局导入布局。
Import layout from components/layout.
杰森 · 兰斯托夫: 好的。
&gt;&gt; Jason Lengstorf: Okay.
杰森 · 兰斯托夫: 我们来看一下,
&gt;&gt; Jason Lengstorf: And,
&gt;&gt; Jason Lengstorf: Let's take a look,
所以纱线工作区内格罗尼斯添加，不，开发。
so yarn workspace negronis add,
no, develop.
杰森 · 兰斯托夫: 嘿，嘿，好了，这看起来好多了。
&gt;&gt; Jason Lengstorf: Hey, hey, okay, so
this is looking a little bit better.